Huh, there's no one anywhere near us.
Death Gun and Xenon aren't on the map, but
counting them, there's six players left.
Huh?
They took each other out.
That leaves four.
Huh?
Thirty players started, twenty-four
are out, so that leaves six.
Me and Yamikaze, then Sinon
and Death Gun, that's 28.
And Pale Rider makes it 29.
We're short a player.
Did Death Gun murder someone
else after he got Pale Rider?
No, his partner's been waiting
at Sinon's for his cue.
He can't be two places at once.
Unless there's another
angle to this I'm missing.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
The pain of the pain, I know that
the power of the strongholds.
I will not be able to die.
The world of the world,
Oh, City,
Well, what'd you find?
There's five of us left.
You, me, Yamikaze.
I didn't see Death Gun, though.
And there's another player
out there somewhere.
The scan didn't pick them up, so they
might be hiding in a cave like us.
That's it?
Just us five?
Well, it's been an hour
and 45 minutes already.
Seeing as how the last BLB ended in about
two hours, this one's right on schedule.
Well, I'm surprised no one's
chucked a grenade in here yet.
Yeah, maybe we've got Death
Gun to thank for that.
Could be while he's looking for us,
he's whittling down the
competition with that rifle of his.
If you're right, then he's a
Shino for the Max Kills Award.
Whatever, we should worry about Yamikaze.
You were probably the only one
who showed up on his terminal,
so we better get ready, because
he'll be coming for you.
He any good?
He was runner-up in the last B .O .B.
He's your typical full-on E .G .I. type.
They call him the run-gun
demon or something.
Uh, run what?
Run and gun?
You run, shoot, run?
It's a style of combat?
His main weapon's a Calico M900A,
an ultralight submachine gun.
Yamikaze couldn't compete with Zexeed's
rare gun and armor in the last tourney.
But even though he didn't win, some
people say he's the better player.
Whoa, he's really that good?
Like the best player on
Japan's GGO server good?
Yeah, he is.
And he might be our ace in the hole, too.
If you're right about Death Gun, then
I'm the only one he's ready to kill.
You know, cause his partner's waiting
back at my apartment right now.
See, I figure that if that's the case,
Yamakaze's not in any real
danger of getting killed.
This is gonna sound cold, but I was thinking
he would make the perfect decoy for us.
When Death Gun shoots Yamikaze,
we'll know where he is.
In a way, we got two decoys.
Him in here, and me IRL.
You're pretty brave, Sinon.
Huh?
Not even.
I'm trying not to think about it.
Trying to avoid what scares
me, like I always do.
Anyway, you think it'll work?
Yeah.
I mean, it sounds pretty good.
Although, there's still
one thing that bothers me.
Just now, when I added up the players
who were left and who were done,
I could only come up with 28.
Pale Riders 29, but still,
we're short one. No way.
Could Death Gun have killed
someone else after he tried for me?
How's that even possible?
I mean, his number two's supposed
to be waiting at my place now.
Right.
That's how I figured it, too.
But now, I'm thinking
something else is going on.
Between the time Death Gun shot Pale
Rider and when he tried for you,
only 30 minutes had gone by.
So based on my theory,
Pale Rider's apartment would have to be no
more than 30 minutes away from your place.
It's kind of convenient, don't you think?
I guess, but what other
explanation is there for it?
Maybe Death Gun isn't working
with just the one guy.
Like maybe he's got a
few more partners if he
does then it'd be possible
to kill one player?
While still having someone
available to kill you
and one for Yamikaze he
could be a target now too.
I don't know I don't
know oh my
god if you're
right and there's more
of them out there how?
How many more are we talking about?
If they're all X Laughing
Coffin, at least 10, maybe more.
I doubt they're all involved with this,
but we can't be sure there's only one
real-world killer out there anymore.
They're crazy.
Why else would they do this
after getting out of SAO alive?
How could anyone stay a
player killer after that game?
For the same reason as us, why
do I keep being a swordsman?
And you, a sniper.
I called them PKers, but I take it back.
There are lots of people
who PK in this game.
I used to run with a
squad of PKers myself.
But at the end of the day, PKers
have a code of honor they stick to.
They're not PKers.
They kill people with poison
while they're unconscious.
Like a bunch of cowards.
There's no honor in murder.
That's chicken shit.
Straight up.
And we can't let them get away with it.
No, we can't.
We've got a chance to stop these
people, and we're going to take it.
Death Gun's going down
on this battlefield.
It's over for him and his pals.
I'll make them all pay.
Yeah, this is how I make
amends for what I did.
For losing it in the chaos of battle.
For killing those two players that night.
And the other one later on.
This is how I'll get closure.
I'll protect Sinon, take out
Yamikaze, and end Death Gun.
It won't be easy, but
it's what I have to do.
I'm gonna take Yamikaze out.
I won't let Death Gun kill him. Huh?
Yamakaze's tough.
I doubt even you could
finish him with one hit.
And if he's busy with you,
Death Gun's sure to go for him.
Then how are we gonna deal with that?
Did you forget what I am?
I'm a sniper.
I'll have eyes on you the whole time,
so once they move on you,
I'll know their locations.
I'll hit Yamikaze first,
then I'll go for Death Gun.
Okay, then.
We go with your plan.
Alright, I think they should
be pretty close by now.
I'm gonna hop on the buggy and head out.
Leave the cave right after I do,
and get set up as fast as you can.
Good luck out there, partner.
Yamikaze is coming from the west,
so if a shot comes from the east,
it'll probably be Death Gun.
He's got that cloak, so when
he shoots, he'll be invisible.
If he hits Kirito in the
harder head, it's over.
But if you can cut my bullet in
half, you can dodge his, right?
Right, Kirito?
My first priority is taking
Yamikaze out of the picture.
If I miss, Kirito will get shot.
Then Death Gun will find me and kill me.
My life, my real life
depends on a single bullet.
Like it did that day.
Please, Hecate.
I'm weak and I need your strength.
The strength to stand up
for myself and move on!
I don't know.
Southwest.
That's Yamikaze.
Don't worry.
Sinon's got him.
Whoa!
What do I do?
I could try to shoot in front of him.
Or shoot at his feet, hope he
panics, and then take him out.
No.
Once he's got Kirito in range,
he'll stop to steady his aim.
I have to wait till he does.
I'll be patient.
Don't worry, Kirito.
I've got your back.
Concentrate.
Home in on his drive to kill.
Like last time.
That's right.
I could feel their lust for murder.
That's how I noticed them.
The first guy who attacked me...
What was his name?
Kirito.
Someday, I'll kill you properly.
Yamikaze.
Get it, though.
Gotcha.
Let's go.
It's up to you now, Kirito.
She did it!
Now it's my turn!
Kirito!
Don't worry, Mommy.
No matter how strong his
enemy is, Daddy won't lose.
He's Daddy, after all.
Yeah, you're right.
Turn left!
His room is eight meters down!
Kirigaya?
Kirito!
Masyuki, right?
We've been expecting you.
Is something wrong with Kirito?
I mean, Kazuto?
No, he's okay.
I know it looks bad,
but he's not in danger.
His heart rate spiked is all.
His heart rate?
Why?
What's going on?
Mommy, look to your right,
at the monitor on the wall.
I'm going to patch in the live
footage from the MMO stream!
Is that...Kirito?
That's Kirigaya's avatar from the game
he's diving in now? Uh-huh. He's in battle.
I think that's why his
heart's racing so much.
An S-Doc?
That's it!
One of Laughing Coffin's leaders
was a master with an S-Doc!
But what was he called?
Sterben?
Isn't it supposed to be Steven?
It's not. But he's right!
It's a German word.
I know it.
It's a medical term we use.
It's pronounced...
Sterben.
Sterben?
It means to die.
In the hospitals, we use that
word when a patient's passed away.
That's an interesting
weapon you got there.
If I'd known there were metal swords in
GGO, I would have gotten my hands on one.
You should have done your
homework before logging in.
Black Swordsman.
I made this with the
Weapon Creation skill.
It can't be any longer or
heavier, but it does the trick.
Wow, if that's the best sword I can make,
then I guess I couldn't
make one I'd be happy with.
Still into swords with
high strength requirements?
You haven't changed.
Must be pretty tough for you, having
to twirl that flashlight around.
This thing's not as bad as all that.
I always wondered what it'd be
like to fight with one of these.
Besides, a sword's a sword.
If I can slash you and burn through your
HP with it, it's good enough for me.
You talk a good game, but it's all talk.
You sucked in too much rotten
air from the real world.
That half-assed Vorpal
strike you just pulled?
If the old you saw it,
he'd shake his head.
Maybe so.
But the same goes for you, too.
You're living in the past.
I bet you think you're still
a member of Laughing Coffin.
You remember.
I'm impressed.
Then I guess you understand the
difference between you and me.
I'm a genuine red player,
while you are not.
you killed only because you were scared
scared and desperate to survive but
instead of facing it I bet you tried to
forget it even happened
just like a coward I
might be a coward but still I'll stop you
from killing again I figured out how sexy
than the others were murdered it's got
nothing to do with that handgun of yours and
you don't have special powers either
how'd those people die then back at the
terminals at the governor's office you use
that cloak to scope out
the addresses of the
bob contestants then you had someone break
into their apartments and timed it so
when you fired they'd inject a drug into
them making it look like they died of heart
failure.
That's how you did it.
The Ministry of Internal Affairs
has the in-game and real-world
info of every single player from SAO.
Once they get your handle,
they'll find out your real name,
your real address, and all the
evil shit you've ever done.
It's only a matter of time.
It's all over for you.
So log out and turn yourself in.
You think you've got it all figured
out.
But you don't.
And you can't stop me.
Want to know why?
Because I know you'll never remember
what my handle was.
You think so?
What makes you so sure I won't?
You don't even remember the reason
you forgot it in the first place.
Think back.
After that battle between
your group and mine,
I tried to tell you my name, but you said.
There's no point in giving me your name.
I don't want to know it.
As far as I'm concerned,
I'll never see you again.
You can't remember my
handle, and you never will.
I never gave it to you, and
now I'm going to cut you down.
I'll leave you lying
here watching helplessly
as I kill the girl and you can't stop me!
Stings, doesn't it?
This is made from the best
metal you can get in the game.
It's armor plating from
a space battleship.
I
don't need one thing anymore.
I want to be stronger and stronger.
I want to be a dream.
Next time, Phantom Bullet.